<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RPU: An Overview on RPU. A GLSL-like language for rendering procedural content</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in RPU: An Overview on RPU. A GLSL-like language for rendering procedural content</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/news/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/news/index.html</guid>
      <description>Initial Release (v0.3.0) - xx of May 2024 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Usage</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/usage/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/usage/index.html</guid>
      <description>From the Terminal RPU can be easily installed as a Rust subcommand.
First, if you do not have already, install Rust and cargo on your system by following the easy steps here.
After that you can install RPU by typing the following command in your terminal:
cargo install rpuc This installs RPUC, the compiler and renderer front-end for RPU. You can now invoke rpuc in your terminal.
If you want to update rpuc to the latest version just enter the above terminal command again.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/index.html</guid>
      <description>Coming soon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/language/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/language/index.html</guid>
      <description>RPU strives to be compatible with GLSL and has a few features that make it easier to write procedural graphics. The language is still in development and is subject to change.
Current Limitations Only signed integers are supported at the moment, i.e. no unsigned integer types and their associated bit operations. As RPU has a rand() function which generates high quality random numbers on the Rust side, I do not see unsigned integers as a priority right now.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>